

# BRAYAN RONALDO MOJICA BARRIOS

Desarrollador Web FullStack

# Contacto ——

(+57) 311 236 6178



(8) 269 6764



ronaldomb98@gmail.com



ronaldomb98



ronaldo.mojica.12

## Acerca de mi -

La presente es mi hoja de vida, en la cual, plasmo mi perfil académico, experiencia laboral, mis referencias personales y las competencias que considero hacen de mi perfil el indicado para desempeñarme como Desarrollador FullStack.

# Acerca de mi-

La presente es mi hoja de vida, en la cual, plasmo mi perfil académico, experiencia laboral, mis referencias personales y las competencias que considero hacen de mi perfil el indicado para desempeñarme como Desarrollador FullStack.

### **DATOS PERSONALES**

NOMBRES : BRAYAN RONALDO
APELLIDOS : MOJICA BARRIOS
FECHA DE NACIMIENTO : MAYO 12 DE 1998
LUGAR DE NACIMIENTO : IBAGUÉ - TOLIMA

**EDAD** : 19 AÑOS

**CÉDULA** : 1.110.590.392 DE IBAGUÉ

ESTADO CIVIL : SOLTERO

**DIRECCIÓN DE RESIDENCIA** : SMZ 5 MZ 3 CASA 16, BARRIO TUNJOS 1

**TELEFONO FIJO** : 2696764 **CELULAR** : 3112366178

CORREO ELECTRÓNICO : ronaldomb98@gmail.com
NOMBRE DEL PADRE : EFREY MOJICA CANIZALES

NOMBRE DE LA MADRE : DORIS NIDYA BARRIOS HERNANDEZ

# **FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA**

# **EDUCACIÓN BÁSICA PRIMARIA**

COLEGIO : JOSÉ JOAQUÍN FLOREZ HERNÁNDEZ

FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN : 25 DE NOVIEMBRE DEL 2008

### **EDUCACIÓN BÁSICA SECUNDARIA Y MEDIA**

COLEGIO : ESCUELA NORMAL SUPERIOR DE IBAGUÉ

TITULO OBTENIDO : BACHILLER ACADÉMICO CON

PROFUNDIZACIÓN EN EDUCACIÓN

**FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN** : 25 DE NOVIEMBRE DEL 2008

### **ESTUDIOS SUPERIORES**

#### **TECNOLOGÍA**

INSTITUCIÓN : UNIVERSIDAD DEL TOLIMA
TITULO OBTENIDO : TECNOLOGÍA EN GESTIÓN
DE BASES DE DATOS

**FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN** : 3 DE AGOSTO DEL 2017

INGENIERÍA

INSTITUCIÓN : UNIVERSIDAD DEL TOLIMA PROGRAMA ACADÉMICO : INGENIERÍA DE SISTEMAS

ESTADO : EN CURSO

**NOTA:** ACTUALMENTE ESTOY CURSANDO SÉPTIMO SEMESTRE DEL PROGRAMA ACADÉMICO.



Desarrollador Web **FullStack** 



# BRAYAN RONALDO MOJICA BARRIOS

Desarrollador Web FullStack



(+57) 311 236 6178



(8) 269 6764



ronaldomb98@gmail.com



ronaldomb98



ronaldo.mojica.12

# Skills

#### **Overview**



#### **Programming**

 $0\ LOC \longrightarrow 5000\ LOC$ 

HTML5 • JS • Python

Java • SQL • LATEX

C • C++ • R

# Projects —

**DecAR** - An augmented reality interior decoration app for Android **CIS\*6320** - An implementation of the Bicubic interpolation algorithm in C++ **CIS\*6650** - A comparative statistical

### **Education**

2015 - 2017 MSc., Computer Science (GPA: 3.7/4.0) University of Guelph, Canada

2009 - 2013 BEng., Computer Engineering (GPA: 4.0/4.0) University of Pune, India

### Research

2015 - 2017 MSc. Candidate, Graduate Research Assistant
Thesis: Data Integration from Multiple Historical Sources to Study
Canadian Casualties of WWI

- Proposed a scalable stepwise deterministic method to reliably integrate datasets without labeled data. The method performs comparably with a method that incorporates a Support Vector Machine
- Constructed a rich longitudinal dataset to enable comphrehensive time-series analyses about WWI Canadian society and military
- Tools: R, Python, scikit-learn, BeautifulSoup, pandas, matplotlib

### **Publications**

L. Antonie, H. Gadgil, G. Grewal, and K. Inwood, "Historical Data Integration - A Study of WWI Canadian Soldiers," in 2016 IEEE 16th International Conference on Data Mining Workshops (ICDMW), pp. 186-193, IEEE, 2016.

## **Experience**

April 2017 - **Data Engineer** Present

Bel

 Currently involved in building a realtime data ingestion pipeline on a Kafka cluster using Spark Streaming, to detect SMS spammers on Bell's network in realtime

Sep 2015 -May 2016

#### **Co-founder & Full Stack Developer**

LocalXChange Inc.

- In a team of 2, raised \$8,000 in funding from The Hub incubator at the University of Guelph, to develop a prototype hyperlocal content platform, aimed at delivering local news and events from community organizations to local users in realtime (i.e., hyperlocal)
- In a team of 3, built hybrid mobile & web apps with Ionic, Angular.js and MongoDB, surpassing 1,000 users within a month since launch
- Met with city officials, including the Mayor of Guelph, and university officials to discuss marketing & business strategies for the platform

Sep 2015 -Dec 2016

#### **Graduate Teaching Assistant**

University of Guelph

 TA for CIS\*2430 (OOP), CIS\*4150 (Software Reliability & Testing) and CIS\*3530 (Database Systems & Concepts) courses

Dec 2013 - **Test** Apr 2015

#### **Test Automation Engineer**

Synechron

- Developed a Keyword Driven and Behavior Driven test automation framework for Microsoft Dynamics CRM. Wrote an efficient recursive function to search multi-level frames, reducing development time by approximately two weeks. Won SPOT award 

  My work opened up a new position in the organization, enabling it to earn additional revenue of \$3,500 per month (estimated)
- Demonstrated by proof of concept that rewriting a test automation framework for Microsoft Dynamics AX, using an open source library (White) instead of a proprietary one (Coded UI), would enable the team to save \$4,000 annually by downgrading the prevailing edition of Microsoft Visual Studio from *Premium* to *Professional*